Shuffle\CardBundle\Entity\Card:
    deck_japanese (template):
        deck: @deck1->id
    deck_korean (template):
        deck: @deck2->id
    deck_french (template):
        deck: @deck3->id
    card1 (extends deck_japanese):
        front: 'おはよう'
        back: 'Good morning'
    card2 (extends deck_japanese):
        front: 'こんにちは'
        back: 'Good afternoon'
    card3 (extends deck_japanese):
        front: 'こんばんは'
        back: 'Good evening'
    card4 (extends deck_japanese):
        front: 'おやすみなさい'
        back: 'Good night'
    card5 (extends deck_japanese):
        front: 'さよなら'
        back: 'Good bye'
    card6 (extends deck_korean):
        front: '환영합니다'
        back: 'Welcome'
    card7 (extends deck_korean):
        front: '안녕하십니까'
        back: 'Good morning'
    card8 (extends deck_korean):
        front: '잘자'
        back: 'Good night'
    card9 (extends deck_korean):
        front: '안녕'
        back: 'Good bye'
    card10 (extends deck_french):
        front: 'Bonjour'
        back: 'Good morning'
    card11 (extends deck_french):
        front: 'Bon après-midi'
        back: 'Good afternoon'
    card12 (extends deck_french):
        front: 'Bonsoir'
        back: 'Good evening'
    card13 (extends deck_french):
        front: 'Au revoir'
        back: 'Good bye'
